import {
  KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
  CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
  CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
  LessonsContentDictType
} from './SharedVariables'

export const Content: LessonsContentDictType = {
  'ア-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ア',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'あ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ア',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'あ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'イ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'イ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'い',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'イ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'い',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ウ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ウ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'う',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ウ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'う',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'エ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'エ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'え',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'エ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'え',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'オ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'オ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'お',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'オ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'お',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'カ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'カ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'か',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'カ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'か',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'キ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'キ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'き',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'キ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'き',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ク-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ク',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'く',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ク',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'く',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ケ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ケ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'け',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ケ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'け',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'コ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'コ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'こ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'コ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'こ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'サ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'サ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'さ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'サ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'さ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'シ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'シ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'し',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'シ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'し',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ス-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ス',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'す',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ス',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'す',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'セ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'セ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'せ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'セ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'せ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ソ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ソ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'そ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ソ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'そ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'タ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'タ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'た',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'タ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'た',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'チ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'チ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'ち',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'チ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ち',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ツ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ツ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'つ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ツ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'つ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'テ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'テ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'て',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'テ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'て',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ト-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ト',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'と',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ト',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'と',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  }
}

export default Content
